Guide to the American Veterans Committee records, 1942-2002 MS2144
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Subjects, 1946-2000; MS2144 Series 1
  - General, 1946-2000; MS2144 Series 1, Subseries 1
    - International Affairs Commission, 1996-1999; Series 1 (Box 259, Folder 1)
    - International Campaign to Ban Landmines, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - International Development Conference, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Invited events, 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Israel, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Israel-Palestine, 2002 (Box 253, Folder 8)
    - Issues, 1952-1960 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Issues, 1987-1989 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Issues Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Issues Committee, 1984-1985 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Japan, undated (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Japanese American Citizens League - Iva Toguri d'Aquino (Tokyo Rose), 1976 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Jenner-Butler Bill to limit the jurisdiction of the Supreme Court, 1958-1959 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Joint Congressional Committee to Investigate Prices, 1947-1948 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Judicial Review, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Judicial Review, 1979-1988 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Judicial Review - H.R. 585, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Kelly, Sergeant Lawrence, 1948 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Ku Klux Klan, 1948-1949 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Ku Klux Klan, 1955-1957 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Ku Klux Klan - Camp Pendleton, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Krum, Tyrell, 1946-1947 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Lane Bryant Award, 1951-1952 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Lary, Virgil - the Malmedy Massacre, 1950-1951 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Legislation re: minority groups and veterans' affairs, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Levine, Milton David, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Lichfield trials, 1946 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Loyalty cases, 1948-1960 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - MacArthur ouster, 1951 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Marshall Plan, 1947-1949 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Mary McLeod Bethune Memorial, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - McCarthy, Senator Joseph, 1953-1954 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - McCarthy, Senator Joseph - impeachment, 1950-1951 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Memorials, 1948 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Memorials, 1987-1988 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Memorial Museum - Normandy, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Merchant Marine [1/2], 1945-1959 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Merchant Marine [2/2], 1945-1959 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Middle East, Turkey, Africa, 1978-1982 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Military enlistments, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Military ex-wives, 1981-1982 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Military justice, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Military justice, 1963-1964 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Military justice, 1971-1975 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Military law, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Military lawyers, 1973-1975 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Military Occupational Specialties (MOS), 1983-1984 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Military Order of the Purple Heart, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Military Reform Caucus, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Military spouses and families, 1982-1983 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous legislative issues, 1965-1977 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Micellaneous manuscripts, undated; Series 1 (Box 259, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous printed documents and newspaper clippings, 1958-2000; Series 1 (Box 259, Folder 3)
    - Mobil Oil Corporation, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - National Action Agenda for the President's Interagency Council on Women, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - National Coalition to Ban Handguns, 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - National Park Service, 1992-1993 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - National Peace Academy, 1982-1984 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - National Salute to Vietnam Veterans, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - National Urban League, 1978-1982 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - National Youth Assembly Against Universal Military Training, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Navy Department, 1948-1950 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - New coin proposal, 1948-1950 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - New project ideas, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - New York National Guard [1/2], 1962-1963 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - New York National Guard [2/2], 1963-1964 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Nixon, Richard - veterans, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Norwegian War Memorial, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - NOW Legal Defense and Education Fund, 1971-1975 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Open housing, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Overseas troop assignment policies, 1951-1960 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Panama Canal, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Partisan political activity, 1948 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Passport legislation, 1957-1959 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Peace Garden, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Peekskill, NY riots, 1949-1950 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Poll tax, 1945-1949 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Post-traumatic stress disorder, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Powell amendment, Federal Aid to Education Bill, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Pregnancy discrimination, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - President's Committee on Employment of the Handicapped, 1968-1969 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - President's Committee on Employment of the Handicapped [1/2], 1973-1978 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - President's Committee on Employment of the Handicapped [2/2], 1973-1978 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - President's Committee on Employment of the Handicapped - subcommittee on Disabled Veterans, 1978-1984 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - President's Committee on Employment of the Handicapped - subcommittee on Disabled Veterans, 1985-1986 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - President's Committee on Employment of the Handicapped - subcommittee on Disabled Veterans, 1987-1991 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - President's Committee on Employment of the Handicapped - subcommittee on Disabled Veterans, 1995-1996 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - President's Committee on Employment of the Handicapped - subcommittee on Disabled Veterans, 1997-2000 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - President's Committee on Employment of the Handicapped - subcommittee on Disabled Veterans, international projects, 1991-1992 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - President's Committee on White House Fellows, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Prison reform, 1974-1977 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Prisoners of war, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Prisoners of war claims, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Proportional Representation amendment, 1949-1950 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Proposal - research study on volunteer army, undated (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - "A Proposal: The Veterans Establishment - Outlook for the 70's", undated (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Proposed trip to New York - Paterson and Harrison, 1948 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Purdue University, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Rankin Pension Bill [1/2], 1949 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Rankin Pension Bill [2/2], 1949 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Reapportionment [1/2], 1959 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Reapportionment [2/2], 1959 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Reapportionment, 1960-1961 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Reclamation, 1947 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Reports on Veterans, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Reproductive rights, 1995-1996 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Retroactive pay, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - "Revolutionary War and the Combat Soldier", undated (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Retirement pay for racially segregated state militia members (H.R. 1440), 1975-1979 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - ROTC program, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Senatorial questionnaire, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Sex discrimination in insurance, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Sex discrimination in insurance - The Non-Discrimination in Insurance Act (H.R. 100 and S. 372) [1/2], 1983 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Sex discrimination in insurance - The Non-Discrimination in Insurance Act (H.R. 100 and S. 372) [2/2], 1983 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Sexual abuse in the military, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Shore, Chester C., 1973-1974 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Social Security, 1984-1986 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Social services in military, 1963-1974 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Solidarity Day, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Sons and Daughters in Touch, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Spain, 1949-1954 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - States' veterans legislation, 1974-1975 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Status of Forces agreements, 1957-1958 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Study Group on Social Security, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Surplus Overseas Supply Plan (SOS), 1954-1955 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Sweatshops, 1996-1997 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Tax reform, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Terrorism, 1986 (Box 253, Folder 9)
    - Thompson, Robert - Arlington Cemetery, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Tobacco, 1991 (Box 253, Folder 10)
    - Training Program for National Veterans, 1947-1949 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Transition Assistance Program, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Truman Doctrine, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Turkish UN soldiers, 1952 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - U.N. Convention to Eliminate All Forms of Discrimination Against Women, 1992-1996 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - U.N. dues, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - U.N. Small Arms Treaty, 2001; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 261, Folder 21)
    - U.N. Technical Assistant Program, 1950-1959 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - United Nations University, 1951-1953 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - United States Institute of Peace Act, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Universal military training, 1945-1948 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Universal military training - con, 1945 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Universal military training - pro, 1945 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - U.S. Court of Veterans Appeals, 1989-1990 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - U.S. Institute of Peace, 1987-1989 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - U.S. Senate Committee on Veterans Affairs, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - VA, 1977-1985 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - VA Agenda for Action, 1973-1974 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - VA benefits, undated (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - VA burial, 1975-1977 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - VA Consumer Plan, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - VA housing, 1968-1980 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - VA - Independent Budget, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - VA - Legal issues, 1992-1993 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - VA realignment, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - VA research, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - VA rural health initiative, 1991-1992 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - VA Voluntary Service, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - VA Voluntary Service, 1978-1985 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Veterans affairs, 1947-1948 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Veterans affairs - Congress, 1983-1984 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Veterans and Armed Forces Affairs Commission [1/2], 1961-1964 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Veterans and Armed Forces Affairs Commission [2/2], 1961-1964 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Veterans Day, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Vets in Europe, 1999; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 261, Folder 25)
    - Veterans' legislation, 1974-1975 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Veterans' pensions, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Veterans and President Carter, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Veterans' and Servicemen's Law and Policy Center, 1967-1972 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Veterans Advisory Commission, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Veterans' Opportunities Day, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Vietnam veterans, 1981-1985 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Vietnam Veterans Day, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Vietnam Veterans Memorial, 1980-1982 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Vietnam Veterans Week, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Vietnam Women's Memorial, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Voting rights for servicemen, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Wallace, Henry, 1948 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - War Claims Commission, 1949-1951 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Washington Area Military and Draft Law Panel, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Washington, D.C., affairs, 1952-1960 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Washington, D.C., Bar Association Military Law Committee, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Washington, D.C., home rule, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Washington, D.C., ratification, 1980-1981 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Washington, D.C., self- determination [1/2], 1977-1983 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Washington, D.C., self- determination [2/2], 1977-1983 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Washington, D.C., statehood, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Welfare reform, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - White House briefing for veterans organizations, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - White House Conference on Aging, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - White House Conference on Families, 1979-1980 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - William Joiner Center for the Study of War and Social Consequences, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Women and minority veterans' issues, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Workshops, 1948 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - World Development Authority, 1952 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - World Veterans Day, 1951 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - World War I pensions, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - World War II commemorative coins, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - World War II Commission, 1992-1993 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - World War II Memorial, undated (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - World War II veterans in the 81st Congress, 1949 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Women's Conference Circle, 1995-1996 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Women's issues / avc, 1995; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 261, Folder 22)
    - YMCA, 1972-1973 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Young Men's Board of Trade, 1945-1946 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Youth Conservation Corps, 1959 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Civil rights, 1946-2000; MS2144 Series 1, Subseries 2
    - Affirmative action, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Audit of Negro Veterans [1/2], 1960-1962 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Audit of Negro Veterans [2/2], 1960-1962 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Audit of Negro Veterans - correspondence, 1960-1962 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Audit of Negro Veterans - Northern survey, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Audit of Negro Veterans - report, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Black soldiers murdered by Nazis in 1944, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Black veterans in the South, 1955-1958 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Civil rights, 1977-1991 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Civil Rights Audit of the National Guard, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Civil rights laws in Washington, D.C., 1955-1967 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Desegregation, 1948-1960 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - EEOC case, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Evers, Medgar - eulogy by Paul Phillips Cooke, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Evers, Medgar - military funeral, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - First Annual Veterans Audit of the AVC, 1955 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Freedom Train segregation - Memphis, 1947 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Health of the Negro, 1953 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Housing discrimination, 1955-1960 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Insurance bill, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Japanese American legislation, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Japanese American veterans, 1984-1995 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Leadership Conference on Civil Rights [1/2], 1969-1980 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Leadership Conference on Civil Rights [2/2], 1969-1980 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Leadership Conference on Civil Rights [1/2], 1981-1983 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Leadership Conference on Civil Rights [2/2], 1981-1983 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Leadership Conference on Civil Rights [1/2], 1984-1985 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Leadership Conference on Civil Rights [2/2], 1984-1985 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Leadership Conference on Civil Rights, 1986-2000 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Leadership Conference on Civil Rights - Special Discharge Program, undated (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Leadership Conference on Civil Rights - Task Force on Employment, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Leadership Conference on Civil Rights - Task Force on Veterans and Military Affairs, 1973-1975 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Leadership Conference on Civil Rights - Task Force on Veterans and Military Affairs [1/2], 1976-1978 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Leadership Conference on Civil Rights - Task Force on Veterans and Military Affairs [2/2], 1976-1978 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Mormon Church, 1962 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - NAACP, 1961-1982 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Nondiscrimination in Insurance Act, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Office for Civil Rights, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Position of United States Senators on the AVC civil rights questionnaires, 1959 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Project AHEAD, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - President's Committee on Equal Opportunity in the Armed Forces, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Racial discrimination in housing, 1951-1966 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Racial discrimination in schools, 1951-1953 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Racial discrimination in St. Louis swimming pools, 1949 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Racial integration - 4-H Clubs, 1962-1966 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Racial segregation in school construction, 1956 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Racial segregation in universities, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Reorganization Task Force on Civil Rights, 1977-1978 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Report on Negro Veterans in the South, undated (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Riggs National Bank, 1960 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Second Morrill Act, 1977-1998 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - School integration, 1960-1961 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Title VI, 1976-1978 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Voting Rights Act, 1980-1982 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Watts, Raymond, 1957 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - WOOK radio, 1952 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Women veterans, 1946-2000; MS2144 Series 1, Subseries 3
    - Advisory Committee on Women Veterans, 1980-1988 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Advisory Committee on Women Veterans, 1992-1993 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Advisory Panel on Women, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Army Research Institute correspondence, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Cadet nurses, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Concerns of women veterans, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Contacts with Women Veterans' Organizations, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence re: women in the military, 1982-1991 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - DACOWITS, 1974-1976 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - DACOWITS, 1980-1983 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - DACOWITS anniversary meeting, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - DACOWITS annual meeting, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - DACOWITS endorsements, 1980-1982 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - DACOWITS executive committee meetings [1/2], 1980-1984 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - DACOWITS executive committee meetings [2/2], 1980-1984 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - DACOWITS proposal, 1980-1981 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Demographic information on women veterans, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Department of Labor programs, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Department of Labor, Secretary's Committee on Veterans' Employment [1/2], 1986-1988 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Department of Labor, Secretary's Committee on Veterans' Employment [2/2], 1986-1988 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Devilbiss, M.C., 1980-1981 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Employment Experience of Women Veterans Placed by Selected Public Employment Offices, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - An Examination of the Employment and Training of Women Veterans, 1985 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Fass, Evelyn, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Ford Foundation, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Ford Foundation - 1st Report, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Ford Foundation - 2nd Report, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Ford Foundation - correspondence, 1978-1981 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Ford Foundation financial report, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Ford Foundation project on women veterans, 1978-1980 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Ford Foundation - proposal appendices, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Forum on Women Veterans' Employment Issues, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Greenspan, Harry, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Harvard Medical School, 1978 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Women Vets - healthcare testimony, 1992; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 261, Folder 23)
    - House Veterans Committee Hearings on Woman Veterans, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Kanton, Joel - women veterans, 1979-1981 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Military occupational specialties for women, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - National women veterans memorial, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - National Women Veterans Recognition Week, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - O'Brien, Thomas - women veterans, 1984-1987 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Proposal - conference on women, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Proposal - Enhancing Employment Oppurtunities for Women Veterans, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Proposal for a Pilot Study: Women Veterans and the VA Hospital System, undated (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Proposal - Returning Women Veterans Meeting Employment Goals, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Proposal - statistics, Women veterans [1/2], 1978-1979 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Proposal - statistics, Women veterans [2/2], 1978-1979 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Proposal - Women Veterans in the Labor Force, undated (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Proposals - Women veterans [1/5], 1978-1983 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Proposals - Women veterans [2/5], 1978-1983 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Proposals - Women veterans [3/5], 1978-1983 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Proposals - Women veterans [4/5], 1978-1983 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Proposals - Women veterans [5/5], 1978-1983 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Research Project - An Exploratory Study on Women Veterans: A Forgotten Population, undated (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Response to AVC report on Employment Experience of Women Veterans, undated (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Salute to Female Veterans, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Segal, Mady, undated (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Sexual abuse in the military [1/2], 1992 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Sexual abuse in the military [2/2], 1992 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - The Status of Women Veterans in the United States and Abroad, undated (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - The Status of Women Veterans around the World - foundation correspondence, 1981 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - VA correspondence re: study of female veterans, 1979-1980 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - VA women's department, 1989 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - VA Women Veterans Program, 1992-1994 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - VAAPOW correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - VAAPOW correspondence with Robert Nimmo, 1977-1984 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - VAAPOW proposal to VA, 1980 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Veterans' employment, 1985-1988 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Vietnam Women's Memorial Project hearing, 1988 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - WASPS, 1977-1980 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - WE WACS, 1981-1982 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Willenz articles on women veterans, undated (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - WIMSA [1/2], 1986-1988 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - WIMSA [2/2], 1986-1988 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - WIMSA [1/2], 1987-2000 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - WIMSA [2/2], 1987-2000 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - WIMSA - advisory committee correspondence, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - WIMSA Articles of Incorporation, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - WIMSA - AVC plaque, 1991-1992 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - WIMSA - AVC's role, Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 261, Folder 24)
    - WIMSA - AVC statement of expenses, 1986-1988 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - WIMSA - AVC testimony, undated (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - WIMSA - BPW USA, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - WIMSA - brochure, undated (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - WIMSA - Commemorative works, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - WIMSA Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - WIMSA deposits, undated (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - WIMSA donations, undated (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - WIMSA - founding, 1983-1994 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - WIMSA - fundraising, 1986-1987 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - WIMSA meeting minutes, 1987-1988 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - WIMSA National Advisory Committee, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - WIMSA - National Capitol Memorial Advisory Committee hearing, undated (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - WIMSA - National Park Service, 1986-1987 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - WIMSA - Oakar, Mary Rose (Congressman), 1985-1986 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - WIMSA plan of action, undated (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - WIMSA - press, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 6)